[
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Hello. What _________ your name?",
"correct_answer": "is",
"incorrect_answers": [
"be",
"are",
"call"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Anna: What’s your job? Christina: I’m __________ secretary.",
"correct_answer": "a",
"incorrect_answers": [
"an",
"on",
"one"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "I have a brother. __________ name is John.",
"correct_answer": "His",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hers",
"Him",
"Her"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
},
{
"category": "Beginner",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "He lives __________ England.",
"correct_answer": "in",
"incorrect_answers": [
"on",
"at",
"an"
]
}
]